<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>net.damonlynch.rapid_photo_downloader</id>
  <provides>
    <id>rapid_photo_downloader.desktop</id>
    <binary>rapid-photo-downloader</binary>
  </provides>
  <metadata_license>CC-BY-4.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <name>Rapid Photo Downloader</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Rapid Photo Downloader</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Rapid Photo Downloader</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Rapid Photo Downloader</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Rapid-Fotoübertragung</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Rapid Photo Downloader</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Rapid foto allalaadija</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Nopea kuvien lataus</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Rapid Photo Downloader</name>
  <name xml:lang="hr">Rapid Photo Downloader</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">Gyors Fotó Letöltő</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Rapid Photo Downloader</name>
  <name xml:lang="ja">高速写真ダウンローダ</name>
  <name xml:lang="nb">Rapid Photo Downloader</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Rapid Photo Downloader</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">Rapid Photo Downloader</name>
  <name xml:lang="oc">Rapid Photo Downloader</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Rapid Photo Downloader</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Transferidor Rápido de Foto</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt_BR">Rapid Photo Downloader</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">Rapid Foto Descărcător</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Rapid Photo Downloader</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Rapid Photo Downloader</name>
  <name xml:lang="sq">Shkarkues i Shpejtë Fotosh</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr">Брзи преносилац фотографија</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Rapid Photo Downloader</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Rapid Photo Downloader</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Rapid Photo Downloader</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_CN">快速照片下载器</name>
  <summary>Download, rename and back up photos and videos from cameras and other devices</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Stahování, přejmenovávání a zálohování fotografií a videí z fotoaparátů a dalších zařízení</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Fotos und Videos von Kameras oder anderen Geräten und Speichermedien übertragen und/oder umbenennen sowie Sicherheitskopien erstellen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Κατεβάστε, αλλάξτε όνομα και κάνετε αντίγραφα ασφαλείας φωτογραφιών και βίντεο από κάμερες και άλλες συσκευές</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Descargar, renombrar y hacer copias de seguridad de fotos y vídeos de cámaras y otros dispositivos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Transférez, renommez et sauvegardez des photos et des vidéos à partir d'appareils photo et d'autres périphériques</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Fényképek és videók letöltése, átnevezése és biztonsági mentése kamerákból és egyéb eszközökről</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ja">カメラなどのデバイスから写真・動画をダウンロードしたり，名称変更したりバックアップしたりします．</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nb">Last ned, endre navn og sikkerhetskopier bilder og videoer fra kameraer og andre enheter</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Download, hernoem en back-up foto's en video's van camera's en andere apparaten</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Last ned, endra namn og tryggleikskopier bilete og videoar frå kamera og andre einingar</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Pobieraj, zmieniaj nazwy i twórz kopie zapasowe zdjęć i filmów z aparatów i innych urządzeń</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt_BR">Baixar, renomear e salvar em backup fotos e vídeos de câmeras e outros dispositivos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Загружайте, переименовывайте и создавайте резервные копии фото и видео с камер и других устройств</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sq">Shkarkoni, riemërtoni dhe bëni kopje rezervë të fotove dhe videove nga kamerat dhe pajisjet e tjera</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr">Преузмите, преименујте и направите резерву фотографија и снимака са фото-апарата и других уређаја</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Kameralardan ve diğer cihazlardan fotoğrafları ve videoları indirin, yeniden adlandırın ve yedekleyin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_CN">从相机和其他设备上下载、重命名并备份照片和视频。</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Rapid Photo Downloader imports photos and videos from cameras, phones, memory cards and other devices at high speed. It can be configured to rename photos and videos with meaningful filenames you specify. It can also back up photos and videos as they are downloaded. It downloads from and backs up to multiple devices simultaneously.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Aplikace Rapid Photo Downloader slouží pro rychlý přenos fotografií a videí z fotoaparátů, telefonů a paměťových karet do počítače. V rámci toho je možné zařídit aby soubory s fotografiemi a videi byly přejmenovávány na praktičtější názvy podle schéma, které určíte. Dále je možné je v průběhu stahování také zálohovat. Stahovat a zálohovat je možné z a na vícero zařízení naráz.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Rapid Photo Downloader importiert Fotos und Videos von Kameras, Telefonen, Speicherkarten und anderen Geräten mit hoher Geschwindigkeit. Es erlaubt das Umbenennen von Fotos und Videos in von Ihnen festgelegte, sprechende Dateinamen. Außerdem kann es Fotos und Videos bereits während der Übertragung sichern. Es überträgt von und sichert nach mehreren Geräten gleichzeitig.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Rapid Photo Downloader importa fotos y vídeos de cámaras, teléfonos, tarjetas de memora y otros dispositivos a alta velocidad. Se puede configurar para renombrar fotos y vídeos con nombres significativos que indique. También puede hacer copias de seguridad de fotos y vídeo según se descargan. Descarga y hace copias de seguridad de varios dispositivos simultáneamente.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Rapid Photo Downloader importe des photos et des vidéos depuis des appareils photo, des téléphones, des cartes mémoires et d'autres périphériques à haute vitesse. Il peut être configuré pour renommer des photos et des vidéos avec des noms de fichiers significatifs que vous spécifiez. Il peut également sauvegarder des photos et des vidéos lorsqu'elles sont transférées. Il télécharge et sauvegarde sur plusieurs périphériques simultanément.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A Rapid Photo Downloader nagy sebességgel importál fényképeket és videókat kamerákból, telefonokból, memóriakártyákból és más eszközökből. Úgy van beállítva, hogy átnevezzen fényképeket és videókat a megadott fájlnevekkel. A képek és videók biztonsági másolata is letölthető. Egyszerre több eszközről tölt le és több eszközt támogat.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">高速写真ダウンローダは，カメラや携帯，メモリカードなどのデバイスから，高速で写真や動画を取り込みます．写真や動画は，指定した意味ある名前に変更されるように設定することができます．ダウンロード中に写真・動画をバックアップすることも可能です．複数のデバイスからダウンロードするのと並行してバックアップも行うことができます．</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Rapid Photo Downloader importeert zeer snel foto's en video's van camera's, smartphones, geheugenkaartjes en andere apparaten. Het kan zo ingesteld worden dat het foto's en video's hernoemt naar betekenisvolle namen die je aangeeft. Het kan ook je foto's en video's back-uppen terwijl je ze downloadt. Het downloadt van en maakt back-ups naar meerdere apparaten simultaan.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Rapid Photo Downloader importuje zdjęcia i filmy z aparatów, telefonów, kart pamięci i innych urządzeń z dużą prędkością. Można go skonfigurować do zmiany nazw zdjęć i filmów z określonymi nazwami plików. Może także tworzyć kopie zapasowe zdjęć i filmów podczas ich pobierania. Pobiera i tworzy kopie zapasowe z wielu urządzeń jednocześnie.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">Rapid Photo Downloader importa fotos e vídeos de câmeras, smartphones, cartões de memória e outros dispositivos em alta velocidade. Ele pode ser configurado para renomear fotos e vídeos com nomes de arquivos legiveis de acordo com o que você especificar. Ele também pode salvar cópias de segurança das fotos e vídeos conforme elas forem baixadas. Ele baixa e salva em múltiplos dispositivos simultaneamente.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Rapid Photo Downloader импортирует фото и видео с камер, телефонов, карт памяти и других устройств на высокой скорости. Он может быть настроен для переименования фото и видео осмысленными именами, заданными вами. Он также может создавать во время загрузки резервные копии фото и видео. Он загружает с и создает резервные копии на нескольких устройствах одновременно.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sq">Shkarkuesi i Shpejtë i Fotove importon foto dhe video nga kamerat, telefonat, kartat e kujtesës dhe pajisjet e tjera me shpejtësi të lartë. Mund të konfigurohet për të riemërtuar fotot dhe videot me emra të kuptimplote të skedarëve që specifikoni. Gjithashtu mund të rezervojë fotografi dhe video ndërsa shkarkohen. Shkarkon dhe rezervon njëkohësisht në pajisje të shumta.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Брзи преносилац фотографија увози фотографије и снимке са фото-апарата, телефона, меморијских картица и осталих уређаја великом брзином. Може бити подешен да преименује фотографије и снимке схавтљивим називима датотека које наведете. Може такође да направи резерве фотографија и снимака по њиховом преузимању. Преузима са и прави резерву на више уређаја истовремено.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Rapid Photo Downloader kameralardan, telefonlardan, hafıza kartlarından ve diğer cihazlardan yüksek hızda fotoğraf ve video aktarır. Belirlediğiniz anlamlı dosya adları ile fotoğrafları ve videoları yeniden adlandırmak üzere yapılandırılabilir. Ayrıca fotoğrafları ve videoları indirilirken yedekleyebilir. Aynı anda birden fazla cihazdan indirir ve yedekler.</p>
    <p>Unique to Rapid Photo Downloader is its Timeline, which groups photos and videos based on how much time elapsed between consecutive shots. Use it to identify photos and videos taken at different periods in a single day or over consecutive days.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Funkcí kterou naleznete pouze v aplikaci Rapid Photo Downloader je časová osa, která seskupuje fotografie a videa na základě toho, kolik času uplynulo mezi po sobě jdoucími snímky. Slouží k identifikaci fotografií a videí, pořízených v různých obdobích jednoho nebo vícero po sobě jdoucích dnů.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Einzigartig an Rapid Photo Downloader ist seine Zeitleiste, die Fotos und Videos in Abhängigkeit von der Zeitspanne, die zwischen den Aufnahmen vergangen ist, gruppiert. Verwenden Sie sie, um Fotos und Videos zuzuordnen, die über einen Tag verteilt oder an aufeinanderfolgenden Tagen aufgenommen wurden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Una característica única de Rapid Photo Downloader es su línea de tiempo, que agrupa fotos y vídeos en base al tiempo transcurrido entre disparos consecutivos. Úselo para identificar fotos y vídeos tomados en diferentes períodos en un solo día o en varios días consecutivos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Une des spécificités de Rapid Photo Downloader est sa chronologie, qui regroupe des photos et des vidéos en fonction du temps écoulé entre les prises consécutives. Utilisez-le pour identifier les photos et les vidéos prises à différentes périodes dans une journée ou pendant plusieurs jours consécutifs.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A Rapid Photo Downloader egyedülálló eleme az idővonal, amely a fotókat és videókat csoportosítja az egymást követő felvételek között eltelt idő alapján. Használja azt a fotók és videók azonosítására, amelyek különböző időszakokban, egyetlen nap alatt vagy egymást követő napokon készülnek.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">高速写真ダウンローダに特徴的なものとして時間軸があります．これは，撮影間の経過時間によって写真や動画をグループ化するものです．1日もしくは数日内の別の時間帯に撮られた写真や動画を認識するのにお使いください．</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Uniek voor Rapid Photo Downloader is zijn Tijdslijn, die foto's en video's groepeert gebaseerd op de verlopen tijd tussen opeenvolgende opnames. Gebruik het om foto's en video's te identificeren op verschillende periodes in één dag of over opeenvolgende dagen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Unikalną funkcją Rapid Photo Downloader jest oś czasu, która grupuje zdjęcia i filmy na podstawie czasu, jaki upłynął między kolejnymi zdjęciami. Użyj go, aby zidentyfikować zdjęcia i filmy zrobione w różnych okresach w ciągu jednego dnia lub w ciągu kolejnych dni.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">Recurso importante para o Rapid Photo Downloader é a sua Timeline, que agrupa fotos e vídeos baseados no tempo decorrido entre fotos consecutivas. Use-o para identificar fotos e vídeos tiradas em diferentes períodos de um dia ou em dias consecutivos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Особенность Rapid Photo Downloader - его Шкала времени, на которой фото и видео группируются на основании времени, прошедшего между снимками. Используйте это для определения фото и видео, снятых в разное время одного дня, или за несколько дней.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sq">E veçantë për Shkarkuesin e Shpejtë të Fotove është Kohështrirja e tij, e cila grupon fotot dhe videot bazuar në sa kohë ka kaluar midis shkrepjeve radhazi. Përdoreni atë për të identifikuar fotot dhe videot e bëra në periudha të ndryshme në një ditë të vetme ose në ditë rresht.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Јединствено за Брзог преносиоца фотографија је његова временска линија, која групише фотографије и снимке на основу тога колико је времена прошло између узастопних снимака. Користите је да препознате фотографије и снимке снимљене у различитим периодима у једном дану или у току узастопних дана.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Rapid Photo Downloader'a özgü olan, fotoğraf ve videoları ardışık çekimler arasında geçen süreye bağlı olarak gruplandıran Zaman Çizelgesidir. Tek bir günde veya ardışık günlerde farklı dönemlerde çekilmiş fotoğrafları ve videoları tanımlamak için kullanın.</p>
    <p>Written by a photographer for professional and amateur photographers, Rapid Photo Downloader is easy to configure and use. Program preferences are configured without the need for complicated codes. Common tasks can be automated, such as unmounting a memory card when the download is complete.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Vytvořena fotografem a určena pro profesionály i amatéry, aplikace Rapid Photo Downloader se snadno nastavuje a používá. Předvolby aplikace je možné nastavovat bez komplikovaného programování. Běžné úkony je možné automatizovat, jako například odpojení (unmount) paměťové karty po dokončení stahování.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Von einem Fotografen entwickelt ist Rapid Photo Downloader für professionelle und Amateur-Fotografen gleichermaßen einfach einzurichten und zu verwenden. Voreinstellungen des Programms werden ohne komplizierte Codes konfiguriert. Häufige Aufgaben lassen sich automatisieren, beispielsweise das Aushängen einer Speicherkarte nach erfolgreicher Übertragung.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Escrito por un fotógrafo para fotógrafos profesionales y aficionados, Rapid Photo Downloader es fácil de configurar y usar. Las preferencias del programa se configuran sin la necesidad de códigos complicados. Las tareas habituales se pueden automatizar, tales como el desmontado de una tarjeta de memoria cuando la descarga se completa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Écrit par un photographe pour les photographes professionnels et amateurs, Rapid Photo Downloader est facile à configurer et à utiliser. Les préférences du programme sont configurées sans utiliser de codes compliqués. Les tâches courantes peuvent être automatisées, telles que le démontage d'une carte mémoire lorsque le transfert est terminé.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A professzionális és amatőr fotográfus által készített Rapid Photo Downloader könnyen konfigurálható és használható. A programbeállítások bonyolult kódok nélkül konfigurálhatók. A szokásos feladatok automatizálhatók, például a memóriakártya eltávolítása a letöltés befejezésekor.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">高速写真ダウンローダは，プロ・アマ写真家用に写真家が作成してあるので，簡単に設定を行って使用することができます．プログラムの設定は，複雑なコードを書くことなく行うことができます．ダウンロード完了後のメモリのアンマウントなど，よく行われるタスクは自動化されています．</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Geschreven door een fotograaf voor professionele als amateur fotografen, is Rapid Photo Downloader gemakkelijk in te stellen en te gebruiken. Programma voorkeuren worden ingesteld zonder nood aan complexe codes. Algemene taken, zoals het ontkoppelen van een geheugenkaart als de download voltooid is, kunnen geautomatiseerd worden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Rapid Photo Downloader, napisany przez fotografa dla profesjonalnych fotografów i amatorów, jest łatwy w konfiguracji i obsłudze. Preferencje programu są konfigurowane bez potrzeby skomplikowanych kodów. Typowe zadania można zautomatyzować, takie jak odmontowanie karty pamięci po zakończeniu pobierania.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">Escrito por um fotógrafo para fotógrafos profissionais e amadores, Rapid Photo Downloader é fácil de configurar e usar. As preferências de programa são configuradas sem a necessidade de códigos complicados. Tarefas comuns podem ser automatizadas, como desmontar um cartão de memória quando o download estiver completado.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Написанный фотографом для профессионалов и любителей фотографии, Rapid Photo Downloader легко настроить и использовать. Настройки программы изменяются без необходимости в сложном кодировании. Общие задачи, такие как отмонтирование карты памяти по окончании загрузки, могут быть автоматизированы.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sq">Shkruar nga një fotograf për fotografë profesionistë dhe amatorë, Shkarkuesi i shpejtë i Fotove është i lehtë për tu konfiguruar dhe përdorur. Preferencat e programit konfigurohen pa pasur nevojë për kode të komplikuara. Detyrat e zakonshme mund të automatizohen, siç është heqja e një karte memorie kur përfundon shkarkimi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Написао га је фотограф за фотографе професионалце и аматере, Брзи преносилац фотографија је лак за подешавање и коришћење. Поставке програма су подешене без потребе за компликованим шифрама. Општи задаци могу бити аутоматизовани, као откачињање меморијске картице када се заврши преузимање.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Profesyonel ve amatör fotoğrafçılar için bir fotoğrafçı tarafından yazılan Rapid Photo Downloader'ın yapılandırması ve kullanımı kolaydır. Program tercihleri karmaşık kodlara ihtiyaç duyulmaksızın yapılandırılmıştır. İndirme işlemi tamamlandığında hafıza kartının bağlantısının kesilmesi gibi genel işlemler otomatikleştirilebilir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">Rapid Photo Downloader配置方便易于使用，同为摄影师作者兼顾专业和业余摄影师的需求。 它复杂的代码来配置，自动执行常规任务，如下载完成后弹出记忆卡。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.damonlynch.net/rapid/</url>
  <url type="translate">https://www.damonlynch.net/rapid/translate.html</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.damonlynch.net/rapid/</url>
  <developer_name>Damon Lynch</developer_name>
  <update_contact>damonlynch@gmail.com</update_contact>
  <translation type="gettext">rapid-photo-downloader</translation>
  <categories>
    <category>Graphics</category>
    <category>Photography</category>
  </categories>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">net.damonlynch.rapid_photo_downloader.desktop</launchable>

  <keywords>
    <keyword>RAW</keyword>
    <keyword>ingest</keyword>
    <keyword>memory</keyword>
    <keyword>card</keyword>
    <keyword>filter</keyword>
    <keyword>sort</keyword>
    <keyword>select</keyword>
    <keyword>choose</keyword>
    <keyword>automate</keyword>
    <keyword>workflow</keyword>
  </keywords>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
        <caption>The main window</caption>
        <caption xml:lang="ca">La finestra principal</caption>
        <caption xml:lang="cs">Hlavní okno</caption>
        <caption xml:lang="da">Hovedvinduet</caption>
        <caption xml:lang="de">Das Hauptfenster</caption>
        <caption xml:lang="el">Το κύριο παράθυρο</caption>
        <caption xml:lang="es">La ventana principal</caption>
        <caption xml:lang="fr">La fenêtre principale</caption>
        <caption xml:lang="hu">A főablak</caption>
        <caption xml:lang="ja">メインウィンドウ</caption>
        <caption xml:lang="nb">Hovedvindu</caption>
        <caption xml:lang="nl">Hoofdvenster</caption>
        <caption xml:lang="nn">Hovudvindauget</caption>
        <caption xml:lang="pl">Okno główne</caption>
        <caption xml:lang="pt_BR">A tela principal</caption>
        <caption xml:lang="ru">Главное окно</caption>
        <caption xml:lang="sq">Dritarja kryesore</caption>
        <caption xml:lang="sr">Главни прозор</caption>
        <caption xml:lang="tr">Ana pencere</caption>
        <image width="1600" type="source" height="900">https://www.damonlynch.net/rapid/metainfo/2020/03/mainwindow.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
        <caption>Renaming</caption>
        <caption xml:lang="cs">Přejmenování</caption>
        <caption xml:lang="da">Omdøbning</caption>
        <caption xml:lang="de">Umbennennung</caption>
        <caption xml:lang="es">Renombrando</caption>
        <caption xml:lang="fr">Renommage</caption>
        <caption xml:lang="hu">Átnevezés</caption>
        <caption xml:lang="ja">名前を変更しています</caption>
        <caption xml:lang="nb">Gi nytt navn</caption>
        <caption xml:lang="nl">Hernoemen</caption>
        <caption xml:lang="pl">Zmiana nazwy</caption>
        <caption xml:lang="pt_BR">Renomeando</caption>
        <caption xml:lang="ru">Переименование</caption>
        <caption xml:lang="sq">Riemërtimi</caption>
        <caption xml:lang="sr">Преименујем</caption>
        <caption xml:lang="tr">Yeniden Adlandırma</caption>
        <image width="1600" type="source" height="900">https://www.damonlynch.net/rapid/metainfo/2020/03/photorename.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
</component>